RESUME   OBJECTIVE
"Web Developer with 5+ years of experience in designing and developing user interfaces,testing, debugging, and training staff within eCommerce technologies. Proven ability in optimizingweb functionalities that"
improve data retrieval and workflow efficiencies.
EXPERIENCE
WEB DEVELOPER
"Grooming Technologies, Fullerton, CA I September 2016 • Present"
"•   Revamped web application security applications,minimizing hacker attacks from 2.3% to 0.02%"
"• Designed and developed user-friendly website,including optimized check-out page that increased user clicks,and subsequently customer purchases by 20%"
"• Trained over 50 staff members in internal web functions,including steps on how to independently make minor updates and changes"
• Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed
WEB DEVELOPER
"Focus Solutions, Fullerton, CA I June 2013 - August 2016"
"• Developed dynamic and interactive website that ensured high traffic,page views, and user experience,resulting in 40% increase in sales revenue"
• Oversaw full lifecycle of software development for 9 projects with 100% on-time delivery while staying 5% under budget
"• Implemented server that expedited document generation and search functiona lity by 20%,earning commendation and award from upper management"
• Designed processes for cleanup and performance improvement
that minimized downtime by 13%
111      youremail@gmail.com
\..   895 555 555
"111 4397 Aaron Smith Drive Harrisburg, PA 17101"
in  linkedin.com/in/yourprofile
SKILLS
PHP I PERL I Access Oracle I .NET I CSS ASP I SQL I JavaScript Visual Basic
XML I C# I Ajax I HTML
WordPress Dreamweaver Photoshop
EDUCATIO N
"B.S. WEB DEVELOPMENT California State University Fullerton,CA  I 2013"
A.A.PROGRAMMING Fullerton College
"Fullerton,CA I 2010"
CERTIFIEDJAVA PROGRAMMER
2010
